Guide to the Duke Endowment Archives, 1902-2018 and undated, bulk 1925-2006 RL.00332
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Controller's Office Series (RESTRICTED), 1924-2008 and undated
  - Miscellaneous Subseries, 1928-2006
    - Audit Committee:
      - Audit reports, correspondence, 1964-1973 (Box CO 24)
      - Minutes and Related Documents, 1974-1999, 2005-2007, 8 folders (Box CO 24)
    - Worksheets, Reallocation of Income, A and B, 1924-1928, 2 folders (Box CO 24)
- Investment Office Series (RESTRICTED), 1924-2000, 6 boxes
  Includes correspondence, files for companies that include primarily correspondence and reports, and minutes and related documents of the Investment Committee.
  Arranged by type of material, then chronologically. Company files are arranged alphabetically by the name of the company.
  - Correspondence, 1924-1960, 21 folders (Box IO 1)
  - Correspondence, Company Files:
    - Aluminum, Ltd. 1953 (Box IO 1)
    - Duke Power Company, 1934-1960, 4 folders (Box IO 1)
    - Durham and Southern Railway Co., 1912-1949 (Box IO 1)
    - Erwin Cotton Mills Co., 1923-1940 (Box IO 2)
    - Guaranty Trust Company of New York, 1946 (Box IO 2)
    - Kingsport Press, Inc., 1924-1943, 3 folders (Box IO 2)
    - Niagara-Hudson Power Co., 1935-1944 (Box IO 2)
    - Partalma Company, Ltd., 1939-1940 (Box IO 2)
    - Saguenay Power Co., Ltd., 1927-1947 (Box IO 2)
    - The Stephens Co., 1920-1949 (Box IO 2)
    - Storaker, Nellie (re: Duke Power stock), 1915-1957 and undated (Box IO 2)
  - Correspondence, Duke University, 1969-1970, 2 folders (Box IO 2)
  - Capital Stock:
    - Aluminum Co., 1953, 1955, 2 vols. (Box IO 2)
  - Investment Committee:
    - Minutes and Related Documents, 1963-1974, 6 folders (Box IO 2)
    - Minutes and Related Documents, 1975-1983, 10 folders (Box IO 3)
    - Minutes and Related Documents, 1984-1996, 9 folders (Box IO 4)
    - Minutes and Related Documents, 1996-1999, 9 folders (Box IO 5)
    - Minutes and Related Documents, 1998-2000, 4 folders (Box IO 6)
- Education Division and Committee on Communications Series (RESTRICTED), 1960-1999 and undated, 4 boxes
  Includes minutes and related documents of the Education Division and the Committee on Communications.
  - Communications Committee: (Box ED/CC 1)
    - Minutes and Related Documents, 1963-1999 and 2007, 15 folders (Box ED/CC 1)
  - Educational Institutions Committee:
    - Correspondence:
      - General correspondence, 1962, 1969-1970, 3 folders (Box ED/CC 1)
      - Davidson College, 1969-1970 (Box ED/CC 1)
      - Duke University, 1967, 1969-1970, 3 folders (Box ED/CC 1)
      - Furman University, 1969-1970 (Box ED/CC 1)
      - Johnson C. Smith University, 1961-1966, 1969-1970, 3 folders (Box ED/CC 1)
    - Minutes and Related Documents (Box ED/CC 2)
      - 1960-1969, 12 folders (Box ED/CC 2)
      - 1970-1997 and 2007, 17 folders (Box ED/CC 3)
    - Proposals and reports: (Box ED/CC 4)
      - Davidson College, proposals for special grants, 1986-1988 (Box ED/CC 4)
      - Duke University, proposals for special grants, 1986-1988 (Box ED/CC 4)
      - Furman University, printed material, 1960-1961, 1973 (Box ED/CC 4)
      - Furman University, proposals for special grants, 1986-1988 (Box ED/CC 4)
      - Johnson C. Smith University, proposals for special grants, 1986-1988 (Box ED/CC 4)
      - Johnson C. Smith University, reports, 1961, 1975, and undated, 2 folders (Box ED/CC 4)
- Health Care and Child Care Divisions Series (RESTRICTED), 1923-1999 and undated, 40 boxes
  There are three subseries: Health Care Division Subseries, Child Care Division Subseries, and Health Care and Child Care Committee Subseries. Preceding both subseries is a feasibility study for the funding of hospitals and child care institutions. This series was formerly known as the Hospital and Child Care Divisions Series, and the original names of these two divisions were the Hospital Section and the Orphan Section; except when these earlier names appear as part of the titles of publications, the contemporary names Health Care Division and Child Care Division are used throughout this finding aid.
  - Feasibility study: Report by Alexander H. Sands, Jr., 1924, 3 folders (Box HCCD 1)
  - Health Care Division Subseries, 1925-1989 and undated
    Includes applications from individual hospitals, summaries of statistical information compiled from individual applications, statistics, minutes of committee meetings, surveys, correspondence and writings of Graham L. Davis, and maps showing the distribution of hospitals in North and South Carolina.
    The summaries for hospitals are divided by state. See also Oversize Materials. Arranged in the order in which The Duke Endowment proceeds with the application process and the compilation of data: applications for assistance from individual hospitals, summaries, then statistics. Microfilm is numbered according to the original reel numbers ascribed by The Duke Endowment. [NOTE: This subseries was formerly known as the Hospital Division Subseries.]
    [SUBSERIES RESTRICTED.]
    - Applications for Assistance, circa 1925-1970s (microfilm reels): (Box HCCD 2)
      - Albemarle Hospital - Angel Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 1)
      - Annie Penn Memorial Hospital - Aston Park Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 2)
      - Babies' Hospital - Caldwell Memorial Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 3)
      - Cape Fear Memorial Hospital - Charlotte Community Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 4)
      - Charlotte Memorial Hospital & Medical Center - City Memorial Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 5)
      - Cleveland Memorial Hospital - City Memorial Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 6)
      - Craven County Hospital - Duke University Medical Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 7)
      - Duplin General Hospital - Garrett Memorial Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 8)
      - Gaston Community Hospital - Granville Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 9)
      - Halifax Memorial Hospital - Hickory Memorial Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 10)
      - Highlands-Cashiers Hospital - Highsmith-Rainey Memorial Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 11)
      - Hugh Chatham Memorial Hospital - James Walker Memorial Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 12)
      - Johnston Memorial Hospital - Lee County Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 13)
      - Lenoir Memorial Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 14)
      - Lexington Memorial Hospital - Lowrance Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 15)
      - L. Richardson Memorial Hospital - Marion General Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 16)
      - Martin General Hospital - Memorial Mission Hospital of Western North Carolina (Box HCCD 2, Reel 17)
      - Mercy Hospital - Moore Memorial Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 18)
      - Morehead City Hospital - North Carolina Baptist Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 19)
      - North Carolina Baptist Hospital - Parkview Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 20)
      - Parrott Hospital - Pitt General Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 21)
      - Pisgah Industrial Institute and Rural Sanitarium - Rex Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 22)
      - Reynolds Memorial Hospital - Rocky Mount Sanitarium (Box HCCD 2, Reel 23)
      - Rowan Memorial Hospital - Saint Joseph of the Pines Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 24)
      - Saint Joseph's Hospital - Saint Peter's Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 25)
      - Salvation Army Women's Home and Hospital - Shaw Memorial Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 26)
      - Southeastern General Hospital - Stanly County Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 27)
      - Sternberger Hospital for Women and Children - Swain County Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 28)
      - Taylor Hospital - Transylvania Community Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 29)
      - Tyrrell County Hospital - Warren General Hospital (Box HCCD 2, Reel 30)
      - Washington County Hospital - Wayne County Memorial Hospital (Box HCCD 3, Reel 31)
      - Wesley Long Community Hospital - Abbeville County Memorial Hospital (Box HCCD 3, Reel 32)
      - Aiken County Hospital - Allen Bennett Memorial Hospital (Box HCCD 3, Reel 33)
      - Allendale County Hospital - Bamberg County Memorial Hospital (Box HCCD 3, Reel 34)
      - Barnwell County Hospital - Berkeley County Hospital (Box HCCD 3, Reel 35)
      - Bruce Hospital - Chester County Hospital (Box HCCD 3, Reel 36)
      - Chesterfield County Memorial Hospital - Conway Hospital (Box HCCD 3, Reel 37)
      - Divine Saviour Hospital - Fairfield Memorial Hospital (Box HCCD 3, Reel 38)
      - Georgetown County Memorial Hospital - Greenwood Hospital (Box HCCD 3, Reel 39)
      - Hampton General Hospital - Kelley Memorial Hospital (Box HCCD 3, Reel 40)
      - Kershaw County Memorial Hospital - Marion County Memorial Hospital (Box HCCD 3, Reel 41)
      - Marlboro County General Hospital - McClennan-Banks Memorial Hospital (Box HCCD 3, Reel 42)
      - McLeod Hospital - Newberry County Memorial Hospital (Box HCCD 3, Reel 43)
      - North Greenville Hospital - Orangeburg Hospital (Box HCCD 3, Reel 44)
      - Providence Hospital - Saint Eugene Community Hospital (Box HCCD 3, Reel 45)
      - Saint Francis Community Hospital - Saunders Memorial Hospital (Box HCCD 3, Reel 46)
      - Self Memorial Hospital - Spartanburg General Hospital (Box HCCD 3, Reel 47)
      - Strod Memorial Hospital - Union Community Hospital (Box HCCD 3, Reel 48)
      - Wallace Thomson Hospital - Sample Application for Assistance (Box HCCD 3, Reel 49)
    - Duplicate reel nos. 1-32 (Box HCCD 4)
    - Duplicate reel nos. 33-49 (Box HCCD 5)
    - Applications for Assistance, North Carolina: (Box HCCD 38)
      - Moore Memorial Hospital (Moore County), 1928-1970 and undated (Box HCCD 38)
      - Our Community Hospital (Halifax County), 1964-1969 (Box HCCD 38)
      - St. Leo's Hospital (Guilford County), 1935 and undated (Box HCCD 38)
    - Applications for Assistance, South Carolina:
      - Laurens District Hospital (Laurens County), 1945-1972 and undated (Box HCCD 38)
      - Saluda County Nursing Home (Saluda County), 1968 (Box HCCD 38)
    - Applications for Assistance, Summaries: (Box HCCD 6)
      - North Carolina and South Carolina, 1930-1931, 4 folders (Box HCCD 6)
      - North Carolina, 1925-1931, 9 folders (Box HCCD 6)
      - South Carolina, 1925-1931, 9 folders (Box HCCD 6)
      - North Carolina and South Carolina, 1932-1938, 7 folders (Box HCCD 7)
      - North Carolina, 1932-1938, 7 folders (Box HCCD 7)
      - South Carolina, 1932-1938, 7 folders (Box HCCD 7)
      - North Carolina and South Carolina, 1929-1946, 8 folders (Box HCCD 8)
      - North Carolina, 1939-1945, 7 folders (Box HCCD 8)
      - South Carolina, 1939-1945, 7 folders (Box HCCD 8)
      - North Carolina and South Carolina, 1947-1953, 7 folders (Box HCCD 9)
      - North Carolina, 1946-1953, 8 folders (Box HCCD 9)
      - South Carolina, 1946-1953, 8 folders (Box HCCD 9)
      - North Carolina and South Carolina, 1954-1962, 9 folders (Box HCCD 10)
      - North Carolina, 1954-1962, 9 folders (Box HCCD 10)
      - South Carolina, 1954-1962, 9 folders (Box HCCD 10)
      - North Carolina and South Carolina, 1963-1964, 2 folders (Box HCCD 11)
      - North Carolina, 1963-1964, 2 folders (Box HCCD 11)
      - South Carolina, 1963-1964, 2 folders (Box HCCD 11)
      - North Carolina and South Carolina, 1964 Oct. 1-1968 Sept. 30, 4 binders (Box HCCD 12)
      - North Carolina, 1964 Oct. 1-1968 Sept. 30, 4 binders (Box HCCD 12)
      - South Carolina, 1964 Oct. 1-1968 Sept. 30, 4 binders (Box HCCD 12)
      - North Carolina and South Carolina, 1968 Oct. 1-1974 Sept. 30, 6 binders (Box HCCD 13)
      - North Carolina, 1968 Oct. 1-1974 Sept. 30, 6 binders (Box HCCD 13)
      - South Carolina, 1968 Oct. 1-1974 Sept. 30, 6 binders (Box HCCD 13)
    - Statistics, Institutions Identified: (Box HCCD 14)
      - Hospital, 1945-1951, 8 folders (Box HCCD 14)
      - Clinical service comparisons, 1946-1951, 6 folders (Box HCCD 14)
      - Miscellaneous comparative, 1945-1951, 8 folders (Box HCCD 14)
      - Personnel comparisons, 1946-1951, 6 folders (Box HCCD 14)
      - Hospital, 1952-1959 Sept. 30 (including Personnel comparisons), 8 folders (Box HCCD 15)
      - Clinical service comparisons, 1952-1960 Sept. 30, 9 folders (Box HCCD 15)
      - Miscellaneous comparative, 1952-1960 Sept. 30, 9 folders (Box HCCD 15)
      - Hospital, 1960 Oct. 1-1980 Sept. 30, 20 folders (Box HCCD 16)
      - Clinical service comparisons [ranked], 1960 Oct. 1-1964 Sept. 30, 6 folders (Box HCCD 16)
      - Miscellaneous comparative, 1960 Oct. 1-1964 Sept. 30, 6 folders (Box HCCD 16)
      - Miscellaneous clinical, 1960 Oct. 1-1961 Sept. 30 (Box HCCD 16)
      - Hospital, 1972 Oct. 1-1978 Sept. 30 (Box HCCD 40)
      - Hospital, 1978 Oct. 1-1981 Sept. 30, 2 folders (Box HCCD 40)
    - Statistics, Institutions Unidentified, 1961 Oct. 1-1980 Sept. 30, 19 folders (Box HCCD 17)
    - Statistics, Institutions Unidentified 1972 Oct. 1-1981 Sept. 30 (Box HCCD 40)
    - Group meetings: (Box HCCD 17)
      - 1978-1979, 3 folders (Box HCCD 17)
      - 1981, 1 volume (Box HCCD 40)
      - Statistics, 1978-1980, 3 folders (Box HCCD 17)
    - Instructions for processing applications, circa 1957 (Box HCCD 17)
    - Surveys:
      - Application for assistance survey, 1989, 2 folders (Box HCCD 17)
      - Contracts for compensation of hospital based physicians:
        - identified, 1977 (Box HCCD 17)
        - unidentified, 1977 (Box HCCD 17)
      - Contracts for compensation of specialists:
        - identified, 1974-1975, 2 folders (Box HCCD 17)
        - unidentified, 1974-1975, 2 folders (Box HCCD 17)
      - Paid physician coverage of emergency rooms:
        - identified, 1974, 1976, 2 folders (Box HCCD 17)
        - unidentified, 1974, 1976, 2 folders (Box HCCD 17)
      - Report on the need for additional health services personnel, circa 1962 (Box HCCD 17)
    - Summary Survey: Instructions for computer punch card layout, circa 1972 (Box HCCD 17)
    - Graham L. Davis: (Box HCCD 18)
      - Correspondence, 1927-1950, 16 folders (Box HCCD 18)
      - Reminiscences, circa 1930s; Reprints, 1931-1939 (Box HCCD 18)
    - Statistics: North Carolina, South Carolina, 1935-1954 (forerunner to hospital's comparative statistics, 1 vol. (Box HCCD 39)
  - Child Care Division Subseries, 1923-1989 and undated
    Includes applications from individual child care providers, summaries of statistical information compiled from individual applications, statistics, minutes of committee meetings, and maps showing the distribution of child care institutions.
    Arranged in the order in which The Duke Endowment proceeds with the application process and the compilation of data: applications for assistance from individual child care organizations, summaries, then statistics. The applications and the summaries are divided by state. Applications are then arranged alphabetically by the name of the institution; earlier versions of the institution name are in parentheses following the most recent version. See also Oversize Materials.
    - Applications for Assistance: North Carolina: (Box HCCD 19)
      - Alexander Center (Alexander Home), 1923-1980 Sept. 30, 4 folders (Box HCCD 19)
      - Alexander Schools, 1952-1980 Sept. 30, 4 folders (Box HCCD 19)
      - Appalachian School, 1925-1962 Sept. 30, 3 folders (Box HCCD 19)
      - Baptist Children's Home (Baptist Orphanage), 1925-1980 Sept., 5 folders (Box HCCD 19)
      - Barium Springs Home for Children (Regents of the Presbyterian Orphan's Home), 1924-1951, 2 folders (Box HCCD 19)
      - Barium Springs Home for Children (Regents of the Presbyterian Orphans' Home), 1952-1980 Sept. 30, 3 folders (Box HCCD 20)
      - Boys and Girls Homes of North Carolina (Boys Home of North Carolina), 1957 Oct 1.-1980 Sept. 30, 2 folders (Box HCCD 20)
      - Boys Town of North Carolina, 1971 Oct. 1-1980 Sept 30 (Box HCCD 20)
      - Buncombe County Children's Home, 1924-1952, 2 folders (Box HCCD 20)
      - Catholic Orphanage of North Carolina, 1924-1976 Sept. 30, 3 folders (Box HCCD 20)
      - Central Orphanage of North Carolina (Colored Orphanage of North Carolina), 1924-1980 Sept. 30 (Box HCCD 20)
      - Cherokee Boys Club Children's Home, 1973 Oct. 1-1980 Sept. 30 (Box HCCD 20)
      - The Children's Home, 1924-1980 Sept., 4 folders (Box HCCD 20)
      - Children's Home Society, 1924-1938 (Box HCCD 21)
      - Children's Home Society of N.C., 1949-1965 (Box HCCD 38)
      - Church of God Orphanage and Children's Home of North Carolina, 1947-1980 Sept. 30, 2 folders (Box HCCD 21)
      - Crossmore School, 1970-1980 Sept. 30 (Box HCCD 21)
      - Dunn Children's Home (Dunn Free Will Baptist Orphanage), 1950-1960 Sept. 30 (Box HCCD 21)
      - Eliada Home for Children (Eliada Orphanage and Rescue Work), 1924-1980 Sept. 30, 5 folders (Box HCCD 21)
      - Family and Children's Service of Mecklenburg County, 1964 Oct. 1-1975 Sept. 30 (Box HCCD 21)
      - Elon Home for Children (Congregational Christian Home for Children; The Christian Orphanage), 1924-1980 Sept. 30, 5 folders (Box HCCD 21)
      - Falcon Children's Home (Falcon Orphanage), 1924-1980 Sept., 5 folders (Box HCCD 21)
      - Forsyth Temporary Home, 1928-1935 (Box HCCD 21)
      - Freewill Baptist Children's Home (Freewill Baptist Orphanage), 1924-1942 (Box HCCD 21)
      - Freewill Baptist Children's Home (Freewill Baptist Orphanage), 1943-1980 Sept.30, 3 folders (Box HCCD 22)
      - Gaston County Children's Home, 1929-1935 (Box HCCD 22)
      - Grandfather Home for Children (Grandfather Orphans' Home; Edgar Tufts Memorial Association), 1924-1980 Sept.30, 5 folders (Box HCCD 22)
      - I.O.O.F. Home, 1924-1970 Sept.30, 3 folders (Box HCCD 22)
      - Junior Order Children's Home (N.C.J.O.V.A.M. Children's Home), 1928-1980 Sept.30, 3 folders (Box HCCD 22)
      - Junior Order Children's Home (N.C.J.O.U.A.M. Children's Home), 1970 (Box HCCD 38)
      - Juvenile Relief Home, 1925-1926 (Box HCCD 22)
      - Learning Institute of North Carolina, 1971 and undated (Box HCCD 38)
      - Maxwell Training School, 1925-1931 (Box HCCD 22)
      - Memorial Industrial School, 1924-1971 Sept.30, 4 folders (Box HCCD 22)
      - Methodist Home for Children (Trustees of the Methodist Orphanage), 1924-1951, 2 folders (Box HCCD 22)
      - Methodist Home for Children (Trustees of the Methodist Orphanage), 1952-1980 Sept.30, 3 folders (Box HCCD 23)
      - Methodist Protestant Children's Home, 1924-1940 (Box HCCD 23)
      - Nazareth Children's Home (Nazareth Orphan's Home), 1925-1980 Sept.30, 4 folders (Box HCCD 23)
      - Nazareth Children's Home, 1971 (Box HCCD 38)
      - North Mecklenburg Child Development Association, 1969 and undated (Box HCCD 38)
      - Oxford Orphanage, 1924-1981 Sept.30, 5 folders (Box HCCD 23)
      - Pittsboro Christian Home, 1957 Oct. 1-1971 Sept. 30 (Box HCCD 23)
      - Presbyterian Home for Children (Mountain Orphanage), 1925-1981 Sept.30, 5 folders (Box HCCD 23)
      - Pythian Home, 1924-1955, 2 folders (Box HCCD 23)
      - Pythian Home, 1956-1969 Sept.30 (Box HCCD 24)
      - Quaker Children's Home, 1929, 1932-1935 (Box HCCD 24)
      - Saint Ann's Orphanage, 1924-1927 (Box HCCD 24)
      - Sipe's Orchard Home, 1949-1980 Sept.30, 3 folders (Box HCCD 24)
      - South Mountain Institute (South Mountain Industrial Institute), 1926-1980 Sept.30, 4 folders (Box HCCD 24)
      - Thompson Orphanage (Thompson Orphanage and Training Institution; Episcopal Child Care Services), 1924-1980 Sept.30, 5 folders (Box HCCD 24)
      - The Wright Refuge, 1924-1961 Sept.30, 3 folders (Box HCCD 24)
      - Wright School, 1966-1967 (Box HCCD 38)
    - Applications for Assistance: South Carolina:
      - Aiken County Society for Crippled Children and Adults, Inc., 1963 Nov. 22 and undated (Box HCCD 38)
      - Boys Farm, Incorporated, 1970 Oct. 1-1980 Sept. 30, 3 folders (Box HCCD 24)
      - Brookland Plantation Home for Boys, 1961 Oct. 1-1989 Sept. 30, 2 folders (Box HCCD 24)
      - Bruner Home (Bruner Home for Children, The Salvation Army), 1925-1948, 2 folders (Box HCCD 24)
      - Carolina Christian Home (Carolina Orphan Home; Carlile Courtenay Home), 1924-1980 Sept.30, 5 folders (Box HCCD 25)
      - Catholic Charities of Charleston (Catholic Charities of South Carolina; City Orphan Home), 1924-1980 Sept.30, 5 folders (Box HCCD 25)
      - Charleston Orphan House (Oak Grove), 1923-1980 Sept.30, 5 folders (Box HCCD 25)
      - The Children's Bureau of South Carolina, 1968-1972 and undated (Box HCCD 38)
      - The Children's Home of Kershaw County (Camden Children's Home; The Associated Charities), 1930-1953, 2 folders (Box HCCD 25)
      - Children's Home of Lancaster County, 1972 Oct. 1-1980 Sept. 30 (Box HCCD 25)
      - The Children's Home, 1931-1944 (Box HCCD 25)
      - Church of God Home for Children, 1956-1980 Sept.30, 2 folders (Box HCCD 25)
      - Connie Maxwell Children's Home (Connie Maxwell Orphanage), 1924-1951, 2 folders (Box HCCD 25)
      - Connie Maxwell Children's Home ( Connie Maxwell Orphanage), 1952-1980 Sept.30, 3 folders (Box HCCD 26)
      - Crippled Children Rehabilitation Center, 1963 and undated (Box HCCD 38)
      - Episcopal Church Home for Children (Church Home Orphanage), 1924-1980 Sept.30, 4 folders (Box HCCD 26)
      - Epworth Children's Home (Epworth Orphanage), 1924-1980 Sept.30, 5 folders (Box HCCD 26)
      - Epworth Children's Home, 1968-1969 (Box HCCD 38)
      - Family Counseling Service... Greenville County, (Family and Children Service of Greenville County; Children's Center of Greenville), 1952-1978 Sept.30, 2 folders (Box HCCD 26)
      - Florence County Foster Home, 1957 Oct. 1-1968 Sept. 30 (Box HCCD 26)
      - Freewill Baptist Orphanage of South Carolina, 1960 Oct. 1-1980 Sept. 30, 2 folders (Box HCCD 26)
      - Green Acre Juvenile Protective Association (Juvenile Protective Association), 1925-1951, 2 folders (Box HCCD 26)
      - I.O.O.F. Home, 1925 (Box HCCD 26)
      - Jenkins Orphanage (Orphanage Aid Society), 1924-1951, 2 folders (Box HCCD 26)
      - Jenkins Orphanage (Orphanage Aid Society), 1952-1980 Sept.30, 3 folders (Box HCCD 27)
      - John de la Howe (Industrial) School, 1924-1980 Sept.30, 5 folders (Box HCCD 27)
      - John K. Crosswell Home for Children, 1935-1980 Sept.30, 4 folders (Box HCCD 27)
      - Spartanburg Boys' Home, 1971 Oct. 1-1980 Sept. 30 (Box HCCD 27)
      - Spartanburg County Children's Home (Spartanburg County Orphanage; Green Orphanage; Southern Home Institute for Children), 1922-1940 (Box HCCD 27)
      - Tara Hall Home for Boys, 1971 Oct. 1-1980 Sept. 30 (Box HCCD 27)
    - Applications for Assistance: Summaries: (Box HCCD 27)
      - Thornwell Home for Children (Thornwell Orphanage), 1924-1980 Sept.30, 5 folders (Box HCCD 27)
      - Wilkinson's Home for Girls (Wilkinson's Home for Orphans), 1932-1970 Sept.30, 3 folders (Box HCCD 27)
      - Williamson Orphan Home, 1927-1936 (Box HCCD 27)
      - North Carolina and South Carolina, 1930-1940, 11 folders (Box HCCD 28)
      - North Carolina, 1930-1940, 11 folders (Box HCCD 28)
      - South Carolina, 1930-1940, 11 folders (Box HCCD 28)
      - North Carolina and South Carolina, 1941-1957 Sept.30, 17 folders (Box HCCD 29)
      - North Carolina, 1941-1957 Sept.30, 17 folders (Box HCCD 29)
      - South Carolina, 1941-1957 Sept.30, 17 folders (Box HCCD 29)
      - North Carolina and South Carolina, 1957 Oct. 1-1980 Sept. 30, 23 folders (Box HCCD 30)
      - North Carolina, 1957 Oct. 1-1980 Sept. 30, 23 folders (Box HCCD 30)
      - South Carolina, 1957 Oct. 1-1980 Sept. 30, 23 folders (Box HCCD 30)
    - Statistics, 1927-1968 Sept.30, 50 folders (Box HCCD 31)
    - Statistics, 1968 Oct. 1-1981 Sept. 30, 20 folders (Box HCCD 32)
    - Statistics, 1963 Oct. 1-1970 Sept. 30, 7 folders (Box HCCD 33)
    - Statistics, 1970 Oct. 1-1976 Sept. 30, 6 folders (Box HCCD 34)
    - Statistics, 1976 Oct. 1-1981 Sept. 30, 5 folders (Box HCCD 35)
    - Statistics: (Box HCCD 36)
      - Cost statistics, 1962-1965 (Box HCCD 36)
      - Cost statistics: Group meetings, 1960-1963, 2 folders (Box HCCD 36)